Guide to the Stanley Legum experimental linguistics collection, 1960s-1970s
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Stanley Legum experimental linguistics collection
1960s-1970s
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Stanley E. Legum
C0125
27 linear ft.; 18 boxes
This collection contains research materials on linguistics in the areas of generative-transformational syntax, phonology, reading, psycholinguistics, and sociolinguistics. It includes work by LaBov, Bach Peters, Karttunen, G. Lakoff, R. Lakoff, Chomsky, Ross, Berdan, McCawley, and many others.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Collection donated by Stanley Legum in 1982.
Biographical Information
Stanley Legum studied linguistics and lived in Fairfax, Virginia.
Scope and Content
This collection contains research materials on linguistics in the areas of generative-transformational syntax, phonolgy, reading, psycholinguistics, and sociolinguistics. It includes work by LaBov, Bach Peters, Karttunen, G. Lakoff, R. Lakoff, Chomsky, Ross, Berdan, McCawley, and many others.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged by subject.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Linguistics.
Contents List
  - LSA Handouts, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Mallory, Evonne G., Sequential features in Early Black Child Language (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Master Thesis
  - Toronto Semiotic Circle, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Victoria University, Toronto No.3
  - Papers In Language Use and Language Function No. 7, February 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Papers In Language Use and Language Function No. 8, March 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Papers In Language Use and Language Function No. 9, May 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Papers In Language Use and Language Function No. 10, May 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Papers In Language Use and Language Function No. 11, May 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Working Papers In Sociolinguistics-Darnell No. 57, April 1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Working Papers in Sociolinguistics-Kochman No. 58, April 1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Working Papers in Sociolinguistics-Scollon + Scollan No. 59, April 1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Working Papers in Sociolinguistics No. 88-92, November 1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Partee and Sabsay, Bibliography: Logic and Language, June 1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Working Papers in Sociolinguistics No. 81-87, June 1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Working Papers in Sociolinguistics No. 67-73, May 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Coker, Pamela, On the Acquisition of Temporal Terms, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Geis, M Adverbial Subordinate Clauses In English, February 1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Dissertation
  - Natalicio and Williams, Repetition As An oral Language Assessment Technique, March 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Working Papers In Linguistics No. 11, February 1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Technical Report No. 119, March 1970 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Models for the Reading Process (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Working Paper No. 38
  - Linguistics and Spelling (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Working Paper No. 15
  - Working Papers In Linguistics No. 8, June 1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - How A Child Needs To Think to Read, July 1970 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Technical Report No. 131
  - A Preliminary Bibliography of American English Dialects, November 1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Coker, Pam (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Papers and Resume
  - Melmed, Black English Phonology: The Question of Reading Interference, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Munro, et. Al. Memory for Three Types of Texts, mailed January 4, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Papers In Language Use and Language Function No. 12, May 1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Lakoff, Deep and Surface Grammar, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Cremer and Teplitzky, An Investigation of a Multi-Stage Characterization of Electronics Troubleshooting, July 1969 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Papers In Language Use and Language Function No.1, February 1978 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Papers In Language Use and Language Function No.2, February 1978 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Gass, A Semantic for Relative Clause Formation, Winter 1977 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Kincaid Granddaddy and the Bees, February 1975 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Passow, Secondary Education Reform: Retrospect and Prospect, April 7-8, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Lakoff, If's, And's and But's About Conjunction, April 1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Labov, On The Adequacy of Natural Languages, February 20, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Chomsky, Conditions On Transformations, November 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Kuno, Report No. NSF-20 Mathematical Linguistics and Automatic Translation, May 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Working Papers In Sociolinguistics Nos. 74-80, November 1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Goodluck, Papers In the Structure and Development of Child Language Volume 4 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Lakoff, Report No. NSF-20 Pronominalization and the Analysis of Adverbs, May 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Explorations In Sociolinguistics, Spring 1966 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Lakoff, Linguistics and Natural Logic, April 1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Natalicio and Williams, Repetition as a Oral Language Assessment Technique, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Mitchell-Kernan, Language Behavior In A Black Urban Community, October 1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - McNeill, The Development of Language (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Labov, Learning The Syntax of Questions, June 19-26, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Descriptive and Applied Linguistics Vol. X, April 1977 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Kamei, On the Syntactic Structure in Aphasic Hemisphere-damaged Patients, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Hart, Reading Is Languaging In Print, August 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Bickerton, Pidgin and Creole Studies (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Greenbaum, Acceptability Experiment: Compliance and Evaluation Test, June 1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Baily, The State of Non-State Linguistics (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Salus, The Phonology of 'Three' (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Arderson, et. Al., Early Sign Communication and Skilled Use of English among Deaf Students (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Proceedings of the Eleventh International Congress of Linguists, August 28 - September 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Spatial Networks As A Site For the Study of Language and Thought, Rec'd October 21, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Stotsky, Sentence Combining as a Curricular Activity, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Shih, Unobtrusive Data Collection: An Evaluation of the Appropriate Methodology, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Heller, "Bonjour, Hello": Negotiations of Language Choice in Montreal, July 1978 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Weller, Measurement of the Degree of Bilingualism and Biculturalism of American Teenagers Living in Mexico, 1977 - July 1978 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Deuchar, Diglossia And British Sign Language, July 1878 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Brady, Peer Group Evaluation of Narrative Competence: A Navajo Example, July 1978 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - "Development of a Theory of Language", 1976 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Chomsky, Write First Read Later, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Second Language Acquisition and Language Universals Delaware Symposium
  - Felker and Rose, The case of FCC's Marine Radio Rules for Recreational Boaters, February 1981 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Employment Status of Ph.D. Scientists and Engineers, 1973 and 1975 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Legum, The Acquisition of Adverbial Noun Complements, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Legum, Strategies In the Acquisition of Relative Clauses, December 1976 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Draft: 10
  - Close, An Analysis and Arrangement of Verb Patterns, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - How Sister Got Into the Grog, November 1975 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Doctoral Scientists and Engineers On the United States Profile, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Kiparsky, Phonological Change, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Language Ability Grades, Seven, Eight, and Nine (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Metcalf, Riverside English Preface, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Papers In Language Use and Language Function No. 4, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Driver, The Accomplishment of Inquiry Sequences by Children in informal Classroom setting, August 1977 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Complex Sentences (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Semantics (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Discourse (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Relative Clauses (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - The Acquisition of Comparatives (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Connectives (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Syntactic (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Passives (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Semantic: Organization (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Temporal Terms (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Miscellany (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Pronominalization (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Adjectives (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Particles and Dative Constructions (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Miscellany (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Ajay, Glossary of Style-Related Terms (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Amidon and Carey, Why Five-Year old cannot Understand Before and After (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Anderson, "Subordinate Highest Clauses", 1970 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Annear, Relative Clauses and Conjunctions (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Anshen-Brikerton, Labov, and Inherent Variability (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Anshen, Varied Objections to Various Rules (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Anshen, Some Date Which Don't Fit Some Models (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Anshen, speech Variation Among Negroes in a Small Southern Community (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Bach, Nouns and Noun phrases (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Bach, A Note On Problominatlization (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Bach, Have and Be In English Syntax (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Bach, On Some Recurrent Types of Transformations (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Bach, Anti-Pronominalization (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Back, Pseudo-cleft Sentences (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Bailey, The Patterning of Language Variation (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Bailey, Contributions of the study of variation to the framework of the New Linguistics (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Barclay, The Role of Comprehension in Remembering Sentences (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Berdan, The Potential of Language Bias In and Spelling Achievement Tests For Speakers of (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Berdan, Disambiguation With Tag Question As A Measure or Dialect Comprehension (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Berdan, The Use of Z Morphology By Anglo and Black Children (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Berdan, The Ideal Speech Community In Empirical Linguistic Research (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Berdan, The Use of Convergent Communication for Linguistic Data Collection (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Berdan, Methodological Problems In Assessing Nonstandard Dialect -- A Review of 4 Papers (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Berdan, The Use of Linguistically Determined Groups in Sociolinguistic Research (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Berdan, Probability VS. Obligatory and Optional (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Berdan, Dialect Differences Among Anglo and Black Children (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Berdan, Description of Computer Programming and Processing Needs For Child Language Survey (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Berdan, Tryout of the Annotated Reading Program of Black English (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Berdan, Trip Report on Southeastern Conference on Linguistics, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    (Secol IX)
  - Berdan, An Annotated Bibliography of Structured Elicitation Techniques (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Berdan, Black English for Educators (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Berdan, Development of a Framework for a Theory of Bi-Lingualism (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Berdan, Development of a dialect Differentiation Measure for Black English: A Pilot Study (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Berdan, Have/Got in the Speech of Children (TN) (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Berdan, Development of a Framework for a Theory of Bi-Lingualism (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Berdan, The Necessity of Variable Rules (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Berdan, Probability and Variable Rules: A Formal Interpretation (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Berdan, Sociolinguistic Variation in the Speech of Young Children (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Berdan, A Prototype Diagnostic test For Identifying Speakers of Black English (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Bessemer, Performance of Equivalence Discrimination Tasks By Kindergarten and Pre-School Children (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Bickerton, Quantitative Versus Dynamic Paradigms: The Case of Montreal "Que" (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Bickerton, Inherent, Variability and Variable Rules (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Bickerton, Palenquero: A Spanish-based Creole of Northern Columbia (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Bierwisch, Reviews, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Blaubergs, short-term Memory Limitations of Decoding Self-Embedded Sentences (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Briggs, Visual Confusions With Aural Presentation -- Auditory Confusions with Visual Presentation (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Bransford, Sentence Memory: A Constructive VS Interp Approach (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Brown, Children's Comprehension of Relativized English Sentences (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Carden, Dialect Variation and Abstract Syntax (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Carden, A Problem With Primacy, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Carden, Appositive Relatives and Singular Quantifiers, December 30, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Carden, A Note on Conflicting Idiolects (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Carden, Disambiguation, favored readings, and Variable Rules (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Carden, Double Negatives and Guttman Scales (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Carden, Dialect Variations an Abstract Syntax (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Cedargren, On the Nature of Variable Constraints (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Clark, Some Aspects of the Conception Basis for First Language Acquisition (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Clark, Linguistic Processes In Deductive Reasoning (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Clark, Role of Semantics in Remembering comparative Sentences (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Coker, An Empirical Test of Semantic hypotheses Relevant to Language of Young Children (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Coker, The Development of Before and After, November 30, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Cokman, Why the Only Interesting Syntactic Dialects Are the Uninteresting Ones (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Coots, Teaching Spatial Adjective Comparative Concepts (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Coots, Training and Transfer of Polar Spatial Adjective Knowledge (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Coots, Relational Concepts Knowledge and General Classroom Performance (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Coots, Free Recall of Color Names by Kindergarten Children (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Coots, Relationship Between Equivalence Discrimination and Knowledge of Spatial (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Cromer, The Development of Temporal Reference during the Acquisition of Language (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Current Child Language Resumes, Abstracts from Papers and Reports On Child Language Development (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - DeCamp, What do Implication Scales Imply (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Bailey, Notes on Syntax used by tougaloo students (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Baratz, Beginning Readers for Speakers of Divergent Dialects (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Baratz, A bi-dialectal Task For Determining Language Proficiency in Economically Disadvantaged Negro (Box 5, Folder 3)
    2 copies
  - Baratz, Language Abilities of Black American Review of Research, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Baratz, Early Childhood Intervention The Social Science Base Institutional Racism (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Baratz, Grammatical Constructions in the Language of the Negro Preschool Child (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Baratz, Early Childhood Intervention (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Baratz, Effect of Race of Experimenter Instructions, and Comparison Population (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Bates, Pragmatic Factors In the Acquisition of Word Order (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Bemer, The Economics of Program Production (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Benjamin, Psychopathology and Semantic Interpretation of Ambiguous Words (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Bennett, A Negro Patois Part 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Bennett, A Negro Patois Part 2 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Berdiansky, Spelling-Sound Relations (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Berdiansky, An analysis of the Stimulus-response (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Bernstein, Their Social Origins and Some Consequences (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Bernstein, Language and Social Class (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Bernstein, Hesitation, phenomena and Intelligence (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Bernstein, Social Class, Linguistic codes and Grammatical Elements (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Bernstein, A Socio-linguistic Approach to Social Learning (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Bernstein, A Sociolinguist Approach to Socialization With Some Reference to Educability (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Bessemer, Discrimination of Lifted Weights By Young Children (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Bessemer, An Exploratory Analysis Based on Technical Vocabulary (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Bessemer, Priorities for Research on Concepts Related to Function (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Bessemer, Comprehension Considerations in SWRL Reading Instruction (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Bessemer, The Role of Skills Analysis In Instruction Design (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Bessemer, Retention of Discriminations and an Analysis of Learning Set (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Bever, On the Acquisition Syntax: A Critique of "contextual Generalization" (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Bibliography - ERIC (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Bibliographies -- Scholarly (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Blout, Bibliography On Language Acquisition and Cognition (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Acquisition and Cognition (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Bock, Contributions of Multivariate Experimental Designs to Education Research (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Bloom, Taxonomy of Educational Objectives (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Blumenthal, Multinomial Sampling With Partially Categorized Data (Box 5, Folder 35)
    Board of Education of the City of N.Y. Nonstandard Dialect
  - Bouton, Identity Constraints On the Do-So Rule (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Bowerman, Structural Relationships In Children's Utterances: Syntactic or Semantic? (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Bowers, Adjectives and Adverbs In English (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Boyle, Computer-Scored, Programmed Test Monitors Student Progress (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Braine, The Acquisition of Language In Infant and Child (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Bresnan, In Complementizers: Toward A Syntactic Theory of Complement Types (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Bridgeman, More Classes of Verbs in English (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Brink, Rasch's Logistical Model VS The Guttman Model (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Brooks, A Framework for Science and Technology Policy (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Brown, The First Sentences of Child And Chimpanzee (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Brown, Derivational Complexity and Order of Acquisition In Child Speech (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Bruner, Eleven Hypotheses In Search of a Method (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Butters, What is 'data' In the Expanding Domain (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Campbell, R and D Funding Policies of the National Institute of Education: Review and Recommendations (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Chafe, Foundations of Language (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Chilton, Comparison of Simple Statistical Test for Scalogram Analysis (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Champman, The Interpretation of Deviant Sentences (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Chomsky, Remarks on Nominalization (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Chotlos, A Statistical and Comparative Analysis of Individual Written Language Samples (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Cintas, Southeastern Conference On Linguistics Scecol IX, 1973- (Box 5, Folder 55)
    Bibliography
  - Clark, Linguistic Processes In Deductive Reasoning (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Clark, Semantics in Language Acquisition (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Clark, Deictic Constracts In Language Acquisition (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Clark, General Bibliography In Psycholinguisitics (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Clark, Space, Time, Semantics and The Child (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Cliff, On the Relation Between Unidimensional Judgments and Multidimensional Judgments and Multidimensional Scaling (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Cofer, Adverbial-ly (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Coffman, Essay Examinations (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Coker, Design of the Kindergarten Program Entry Survey (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Coleman, The Simplest Experimental Design That Permits Multiple Generalization (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Collier, Estimates of Test Size For Several Test Procedures Based On Conventional Variance Ratios In the Repeated Measures Design (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Coots, Development of The Language of Comparison: A Literature Review (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Culicover, The Freezing Principle (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Dansereau, Dallas Independent School District Final Report For Targeted Achievement In Reading Program (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Dalby, La Place de L'indice de reference (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Davison, The Indigenous Scripts of West Africa and Surinam: Their Inspiration and Design (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - DeCamp, Clause Connections and Reasons Adverbids (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Decamp, Implicational Scales and Sociolinguistic Linearity (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - DeCamp, African Day-Names in Jamaica (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - DeCamp, Continuities and Discontinuities in Afro-American Societies and Cultures (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - DeCamp, Creole language Areas Considered As Multilingual Communities (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - DeCamp, Dimensions of English Usage, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - DeCamp, The Field of Creole Language Studies (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - DeCamp, Is A Sociolinguistic Theory Possible (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - DeCamp, Mock Bidding In Jamaica (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - DeCamp, Studies In Language, Literature, and Culture of the Middle ages and Later (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - DeCamp, Toward A Formal Theory of sociolinguistics (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - DeCamp, Toward A Generative Analysis of A Post-Creole Speech (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Dillard, Optional Ordering Rules and Genetic relationships In Pidgin-Derived Languages (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Donaldson and Balfour, Less Is More: A Study Of Language Comprehension In Children (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Dong, English Sentences Without Overt Grammatical Subject (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Dratt, The Loss of the Prefix GE-In The Modern English Verb and Some of Its Consequences (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Elliott and Needleman, Hyperlexia and The Relationship Between Spech and Writing (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Duncan, Dominguez Hills Dialect Studies (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Elliott, Exclamations: Conjunctive Questions (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Elliott, Noun Phrases Extraposition In Sentences With Exclamatory Predicates (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Elliott, Toward a Grammar of Exclamations (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Elliott, Legum, and Thompson, Syntactic Variation as Linguistic Data (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Emonds, How Abstract Is Word Order? English as an SVO Language (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Esou, Transition Markers and Paragraph Coherence (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Fasold, Three Models for Dealing with Socially Significant Linguistic Variation (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Feldman, The Role of Underdeterminancy and Reference In The Sentence Recall of Young Children (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Feldman, The Interaction of Sentence Characteristics and Mode of Presentation in Recall (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Fiege-Koilman, Definition and Concept Formation (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Fillmore, The Case for Chase (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Fischer, The Acquisition of Verb-particle and Dative Construction (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Follettie, Number of Measures (n) Required to Evaluate How A Linguistic Will Be Represented (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Follettie, Training Research and Development: lessons from Its Past (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Fonagy, Double Coding In Speech (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Francis, A Teacher's Manual For a Special Program In Freshman English (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Fraser, A Note On The Spray Paint Case (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Fraser, Some Remarks On the Action nominalization in English (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Frasar, Some Remarks About The Indirect Object in English (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Frishberg, Time On Our Hands (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Gaer, Children's Understand and production of Sentences (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Givon, Some Noun-to-Noun Derivation Affixes (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Goals of Linguistic Theory Conference Texas, October 1969 (Box 6, Folder 47)